Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXIX is arranged in 3 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXX is arranged in 4 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXXI is arranged in 11 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXIX. RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 389-0. Resolutions
    - 1925 Convention. General (Box 528, Folder 96)
  - Sub-Series 389-2. Resolutions
    - 1925 Convention. Resolution No. 2. Hospitalization Plans (Box 528, Folder 97)
    - 1925 Convention. Resolution No. 2. Hospitalization Plans, 1925-1928 (Box 528, Folder 98)
    - 1925 Convention. Resolution No. 2. Hospitalization Plans (Box 528, Folder 99)
    - 1925 Convention. Resolution No. 2. Hospitalization Plans, 1925-1926 (Box 528, Folder 100)
  - Sub-Series 389-19. Resolutions
    - 1928 Convention. Resolution No. 19 (Box 528, Folder 101)
- Series LXX. LIFE MEMBERSHIP
  - Sub-Series 394-1. Life Membership
    - Fisher, R.E., Kansas City, Missouri -1925 (Box 528, Folder 102)
  - Sub-Series 394-2. Life Membership
    - Carpenter, S.J., Birmingham, Alabama, 1929 (Box 528, Folder 103)
  - Sub-Series 394-4. Life Membership
    - Mills, W.C., Portland, Oregon, 1931 (Box 528, Folder 104)
  - Sub-Series 394-5. Life Membership
    - Tucker, A.M., Topeka, Kansas, 1932 (Box 528, Folder 105)
- Series LXXI. NATIONAL MEDIATION BOARD
  - Sub-Series 396-0. National Mediation Board
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 528, Folder 106)
    - General, 1957-1959 (Box 528, Folder 107)
      May 1957-59.
    - General, 1956-1957 (Box 528, Folder 108)
      1956-April 1957.
    - General, 1955 (Box 529, Folder 1)
      May-December 1955.
    - General, 1951-1955 (Box 529, Folder 2)
      October 1951-April 1955.
    - General, 1948-1951 (Box 529, Folder 3)
      March 1948-September 1951.
    - General, 1946-1948 (Box 529, Folder 4)
      1946-February 1948.
    - General, 1944-1945 (Box 529, Folder 5)
    - General, 1932-1943 (Box 529, Folder 6)
    - General, 1930 (Box 529, Folder 7)
    - General, 1929 (Box 529, Folder 8)
    - General, 1927 (Box 529, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 396-1. National Mediation Board
    - Personnel, 1945-1959 (Box 529, Folder 10)
      1945-June 26, 1959.
    - Personnel, 1933-1944 (Box 529, Folder 11)
    - Personnel, 1932 (Box 529, Folder 12)
    - Personnel, 1929 (Box 529, Folder 13)
    - Personnel, 1928 (Box 529, Folder 14)
    - Personnel, 1927 (Box 529, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 396-2. National Mediation Board
    - Mediators, 1926 (Box 529, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 396-3. National Mediation Board
    - Blank Forms, 1932 (Box 529, Folder 17)
    - Blank Forms, 1931 (Box 529, Folder 18)
    - Blank Forms, 1932 (Box 529, Folder 19)
    - Blank Forms, 1930 (Box 529, Folder 20)
    - Blank Forms, 1929 (Box 529, Folder 21)
    - Blank Forms, 1926 (Box 529, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 396-5. National Mediation Board
    - Annual Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 529, Folder 23)
    - Annual Reports, 1956-1959 (Box 529, Folder 24)
    - Annual Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 529, Folder 25)
    - Annual Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 530, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 530, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 530, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1932-1946 (Box 530, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1946 (Box 530, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 396-6. National Mediation Board
    - Unsettled Submissions, 1960-1962 (Box 530, Folder 6)
      July 1960-62.
    - Unsettled Submissions, 1957-1960 (Box 530, Folder 7)
      October 1957-June 1960.
    - Unsettled Submissions, 1956-1957 (Box 530, Folder 8)
      1956-September 1957.
    - Unsettled Submissions, 1954-1955 (Box 530, Folder 9)
      February 1954-55.
    - Unsettled Submissions, 1952-1954 (Box 530, Folder 10)
      April 1952-January 1954.
    - Unsettled Submissions, 1950-1952 (Box 530, Folder 11)
      June 1950-March 1952.
    - Unsettled Submissions, 1948-1950 (Box 530, Folder 12)
      November 1948-May 1950.
    - Unsettled Submissions, 1947-1948 (Box 530, Folder 13)
      1947-October 1948.
    - Unsettled Submissions, 1945-1946 (Box 530, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 396-7. National Mediation Board
    - Undesirable Neutral Arbitrators, 1931 (Box 530, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 396-8. National Mediation Board
    - Pending Mediation Cases, 1947-1950 (Box 531, Folder 1)
    - Pending Mediation Cases. Certifications by Union, 1953-1954 (Box 531, Folder 2)
      December 1953-October 1954.
    - Pending Mediation Cases. Certifications by Union, 1949-1953 (Box 531, Folder 3)
      June 1949-November 1953.
    - Pending Mediation Cases. Certifications by Union, 1948-1949 (Box 531, Folder 4)
      1948-May 1949.
    - Pending Mediation Cases. Certifications by Union, 1940-1945 (Box 531, Folder 5)
      May 1940-June 1945.
    - Pending Mediation Cases, 1946 (Box 531, Folder 6)
    - Pending Mediation Cases. Certifications by Union, 1935-1940 (Box 531, Folder 7)
    - Pending Mediation Cases. Certifications by Union, 1941-1947 (Box 531, Folder 8)
    - Pending Mediation Cases. Certifications by Union, 1945 (Box 531, Folder 9)
      July-December 1945.
  - Sub-Series 396-9. National Mediation Board
    - Agreements, 1942-1955 (Box 531, Folder 10)
    - Agreements, 1935-1938 (Box 531, Folder 11)
    - Agreements, 1941 (Box 531, Folder 12)
    - Agreements, 1939-1940 (Box 532, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 396-10. National Mediation Board
    - Withdrawals, 1935-1941 (Box 532, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 396-11. National Mediation Board
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1952-1955 (Box 532, Folder 3)
      August 1952-July 1955.
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1952 (Box 532, Folder 4)
      February 15, 1952-July 1952.
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1950-1952 (Box 532, Folder 5)
      November 11, 1950-February 14, 1952.
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1950 (Box 532, Folder 6)
      June 1950-November 10, 1950.
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 532, Folder 7)
      July 1949-May 1950.
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1949 (Box 532, Folder 8)
      1949 September 19
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1947-1949 (Box 532, Folder 9)
      June 1947-June 1949.
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 532, Folder 10)
      June 1946-May 1947.
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1944-1946 (Box 533, Folder 1)
      1944-May 1946.
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1936-1943 (Box 533, Folder 2)
    - Emergency Board Reports, 1943 (Box 533, Folder 3)
      1943 April 7